INFORMATION DETAIL

AHMAD ADZREIL BIN ADNAN

Permanent Address: Apt Harmoni F-322, Jln PJU 10/1 Damansara

Damai

47830 Petaling Jaya, Selangor

Mobile phone Number: 017-9981001

E-mail: adzreil@sr-two.com



AREAS OF EXPERTISE PROFILE SUMMARY

Java Development
ReactNative
Development
MVC
Designer
Software/Hardware

Troubleshoot

 As an organised and highly creative individual. I love the challenges of working within a dynamic and fast paced working environment. The knowledge gained from my corporate experience from various filed has shaped my ability to adapt quickly, work efficiently and work effectively as part of a team or on my own

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Sr-Two Solution | SALES TECHNICAL ENGINEER

JAN 2017 - PRESENT

Liaising closely with internal design and development teams, responsible to the established sales opportunities of the product. Provide technical services and user guide for any project under the company. Following any business assessment or performing site visit for current on Going project. My responsible also including provide solution architecture. Responsible in project management. Other than that doing configuration for project that using the VMS system Axxon NEXT and Intelect. Creating solution for the VMS project. Revamped current company website into new design.

Key Skills: Project Management | Axxon VMS | HTML/CSS | JOOMLA | Web Design | Customer Support | User Experiences Design | MS Office | Microsoft Visio | HTML/CSS

In-house Application Developer, Octopus Technology

2016 - onGoing

Roles as Mobile Developer such as maintaining and editing existing project application using React Native and JAVA. Developing and maintaining any others application using .NET MVC such as Website. The current project focusing more on React Native. Others languages such as HTML, PHP. Also the implementation of bootstrap.

Key Skills: JAVA | Bootstrap | REACT NATIVE | HTML/CSS/PHP | .NET | MVC | Android Studio | Microsoft Visual Basic | Microsoft Visual Studio

Freelance Video Editor, Seni Media Sdn Bhd

Mei 2016 - Sept 2016

Liaising closely with internal design and development teams to create Advertising commercial videos base on customer request. Provide user guide and storyboard for the videos project according to the suitable of event. Editing and touching up videos so that it following the standard of advertising. Creating 1000 of videos event for MARA.

Key Skills: Adobe After Effect | Adobe Photoshop | Adobe Element | Adobe Premier | KdenLive | User Design |

Associate Engineer, Brilliance Information

Sept 2015 - Feb 2016

- Handling documentation including design and troubleshooting of application, conducting validation of needs in conjunction with onsite and offsite teams.
- Working with onsite client to track status & issues of development
- Completing project development as per requirement, schedules & activities:
 contributing to team meeting. Doing data entry for onGoing project; data miner and following supervisor for site visit

Key Skills: Microsoft Excel | Data miner | Project Management | Troubleshooting | .Net

Graphic Designer, I-Design Sdn Bhd

2010 - 2011

Creating advertising design such as business card, banner, signboard, lightboard and any requested design based on client. Liaising closely with design team to create and completing project according to the time lines

Key Skills: Adobe Photoshop | Adobe Illustrator | Adobe Indesign | MS Office

EDUCATION

University Malaysia Pahang Bachelor of Computer Science (Graphic & Multimedia) with Hons

2011 Sept- 2016 Feb Current CPA score : 2.64

Cosmopoint International College Of Technology Diploma In Computer Graphic Design

July 2007- May 2010
Obtained Cumulative CGPA score: 2.85

SKILLS

- Developed web application and non-web applications using various programming languages and also using CMS.
- Repairing PC/Laptop
- Troubleshooting Software/Hardware
- Develop mobile application for android phone.
- Modify existing programs and find solution error.

COMPUTING

Basic: MS Office | Libre Office | IBM Rational Rose

Programming: Java | C/C++ | VB.NET | ASP.NET | HTML | PHP | SQL | JavaScript | Linux/Unix.
Software: Microsoft Access | CodeBlocks | NetBeans | Eclipse | Adobe Series | Autodesk
MAYA | Houdini | Nuke | Cinema4D | GIMP | Blender | Microsoft Visual Studio | Motorola

Rhomobile Suite | Arduino | Android studio

OS: Windows | Linux

CERTIFICATION

Motorola Solution Mobility Application (2015)

Coursework and Training:

- Introduction to Motorola Mobile
- Object Oriented Concepts using Java
- Developing IOS Application using RhoMobile Suite
- Ruby Programming Language implement

3P Industry-Based Certification Programme Autodesk Certified Proffesional: Maya (2014)

Coursework and Training:

- Introduction to Autodesk Maya
- Implement Maya Script
- Creating 3D Model

REFERENCES

SR-TWO SOLUTION

Supervisor:

Nik NurSyuhada

Email: niknursyuhada@yahoo.com

Contact No: 0134428320

OCTOPUS TECHNOLOGY

Supervisor:

Mohamad Faisal

Contact No: 0129828626